{
    "id": "db976470d0ad4e5a9574af8ac7fe8da9",
    "title": "Personal Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Rita goes to school with ……………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "I"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………………. is my friend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "She",
                "Her"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you help ……………………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is taller than ………………………………. is.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I earn as much as ………………………………. does.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………………. go to school by bus.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "We",
                "Us"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She has lost ………………………………. memory.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We are going for a drink. Would you like to come with ……………………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "we",
                "us"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The invitation was for Jane and ……………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "John and ………………………………. are going skiing this weekend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}